I'm supposed to be the person in charge of magic No. 1.
ฉันควรจะเป็นผู้รับผิดชอบเวทมนตร์หมายเลข 1
I'm in the spiritual world of my mother now.
ฉันอยู่ในโลกฝ่ายวิญญาณของแม่แล้ว
What happened...
เกิดอะไรขึ้น...
No. 1, don't slack off. Get to work.
ลำดับที่ 1 อย่าหย่อนยาน ไปทำงาน
Alright, I get it.
โอเค ฉันเข้าใจแล้ว
Always nagging.
จู้จี้อยู่เสมอ
People who care about relationships are stupid.
คนที่ใส่ใจเกี่ยวกับความสัมพันธ์นั้นโง่
After all, you are...
ท้ายที่สุดคุณคือ ...
She flew so high.
เธอบินได้สูงมาก
Nice shot.
ยิงดี.
It hurts...
มันเจ็บ...
-It hurts! -Calm down, the person in charge of body.
-มันเจ็บ! -ใจเย็นๆ คนดูแลร่างกาย
-Don't we have anti-Gaido skill? -It hurts.
- พวกเราไม่มีทักษะต่อต้านไกโดเหรอ? -มันเจ็บ.
-Yes. Mental direct attack will be offset. -It hurts a lot.
-ใช่. การโจมตีทางจิตใจโดยตรงจะถูกชดเชย - มันเจ็บมาก
-Logically, it shouldn't hurt. -It hurts so much!
- ตามหลักแล้ว ไม่ควรทำร้าย -มันเจ็บมาก!
Why can't you just cooperate with me?
ทำไมคุณไม่สามารถร่วมมือกับฉัน
Because it's meaningless.
เพราะมันไร้ความหมาย
What's wrong with you?
มีอะไรผิดปกติกับคุณ?
Nothing. I was wondering, why didn't mother fight back when attacked?
ไม่มีอะไร ฉันสงสัยว่าทำไมแม่ไม่ตอบโต้เมื่อถูกโจมตี?
Because we have the anti-Gaido skill. Even if she wants to fight back, she can't.
เพราะเรามีสกิลต่อต้านไกโด แม้ว่าเธอต้องการโต้กลับ เธอก็ทำไม่ได้
It would be good if that's the case.
คงจะดีถ้าเป็นอย่างนั้น
Thinking too much can't bring us a conclusion after all.
การคิดมากเกินไปไม่สามารถทำให้เราสรุปได้
Let's go back to the Body after eating.
ให้กลับไปที่ Body หลังจากรับประทานอาหาร
Okay.
ตกลง.
You're right.
คุณถูก.
♫The alarm goes off. My name is Little Spider♫
♫นาฬิกาปลุกดับลง ฉันชื่อแมงมุมน้อย♫
EPISODE 15: DID MOTHER, SEND THESE ANNOYING PUPPET SPIDERS? ♫The awakening survival skill♫
ตอนที่ 15: คุณแม่ส่งแมงมุมหุ่นน่ารำคาญพวกนี้ไปไหม? ♫ทักษะการเอาชีวิตรอดที่ตื่นขึ้น♫
♫No obstacles can stop me♫
ตอนที่ 15: คุณแม่ส่งแมงมุมหุ่นน่ารำคาญพวกนี้ไปไหม? ♫ไม่มีอุปสรรคใดหยุดฉันได้♫
♫Go! Dark clouds♫
♫ไป! เมฆมืด♫
♫Sometimes I pretend it's fate♫
♫บางครั้งฉันก็แสร้งทำเป็นว่าโชคชะตา♫
♫The 3-D perspective street that appears in the intersection of good and evil♫
♫ถนนมุมมอง 3 มิติ ที่ปรากฏอยู่ในทางแยกของความดีและความชั่ว♫
♫The labyrinth of nightmares is nothing to me♫
♫เขาวงกตแห่งฝันร้ายไม่มีความหมายสำหรับฉัน♫
♫Common sense isn't useful here♫
♫สามัญสำนึกไม่มีประโยชน์ที่นี่♫
♫Charging forward like a man is naive♫
♫ พุ่งไปข้างหน้าเหมือนผู้ชายไร้เดียงสา ♫
♫Because life isn't as easy as you think♫
♫เพราะชีวิตไม่ได้ง่ายอย่างที่คิด♫
♫It drives me forward♫
♫มันทำให้ฉันก้าวไปข้างหน้า♫
♫These hands created a brave me♫
♫มือเหล่านี้สร้างฉันให้กล้าหาญ♫
♫Excuse me, I'm the strongest!♫
♫ขอโทษนะ ฉันแข็งแกร่งที่สุด!♫
♫The violent and greedy spider is riding the wind♫
♫แมงมุมที่ดุร้ายและโลภกำลังขี่สายลม♫
♫The unpredictable waves♫
♫คลื่นที่คาดเดาไม่ได้♫
♫It's not the end yet♫
♫ ยังไม่จบ ♫
♫Use the fastest speed to pass through darkness♫
♫ใช้ความเร็วที่เร็วที่สุดเพื่อผ่านความมืด♫
♫Because we only live once♫
♫เพราะเรามีชีวิตอยู่เพียงครั้งเดียว♫
♫As long as we keep running forward♫
♫ตราบใดที่เรายังคงวิ่งไปข้างหน้า♫
♫Loosen the knot in your heart♫
♫ คลายปมในใจเธอ ♫
♫So you can jump right onto the next exciting stage♫
♫เพื่อให้คุณสามารถกระโดดไปยังเวทีที่น่าตื่นเต้นถัดไป♫
Is the vampire child alright?
เด็กแวมไพร์สบายดีไหม?
She seems to have been targeted.
ดูเหมือนว่าเธอจะตกเป็นเป้าหมาย
But it's surely simpler than being a reincarnated spider. She should be fine.
แต่มันง่ายกว่าการเป็นแมงมุมที่กลับชาติมาเกิดอย่างแน่นอน เธอควรจะสบายดี
I have my business to attend to. I should stop thinking about it.
ฉันมีธุรกิจที่ต้องทำ ฉันควรเลิกคิดเรื่องนี้ได้แล้ว
That's it.
แค่นั้นแหละ.
By the way, my parallel wills haven't contacted me since they're with mother.
อีกอย่าง พินัยกรรมคู่ขนานของฉันไม่เคยติดต่อมาเลย เพราะพวกเขาอยู่กับแม่
Things are perhaps going well when there's no news.
สิ่งต่าง ๆ อาจเป็นไปด้วยดีเมื่อไม่มีข่าว
We finally got rid of half a leg.
ในที่สุดเราก็กำจัดครึ่งขาได้
I thought we can never finish this. It seems there may be a way.
ฉันคิดว่าเราไม่สามารถทำสิ่งนี้ให้เสร็จได้ ดูเหมือนว่าจะมีวิธี
Over there, you're starting to slack off as soon as I'm not watching.
ตรงนั้น คุณเริ่มจะเฉื่อยทันทีที่ฉันไม่ได้ดู
Get to work!
ไปทำงาน!
Roger.
โรเจอร์.
Don't you think it's weird?
คุณไม่คิดว่ามันแปลกเหรอ?
Weird? What's weird?
แปลก? มีอะไรแปลก?
Although this is very time consuming, if this goes on mother will surely lose.
แม้จะใช้เวลานานมาก แต่ถ้าทำต่อไป แม่แพ้แน่นอน
Isn't this good?
ไม่ดีเหรอ?
However, she's doing nothing.
อย่างไรก็ตาม เธอไม่ได้ทำอะไรเลย
Mother is too big to go outside, that's why she gave up.
แม่ใหญ่เกินกว่าจะออกไปข้างนอก นั่นคือเหตุผลที่เธอยอมแพ้
How is this possible?
เป็นไปได้อย่างไร?
What? What's going on?
อะไร? เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
Nothing. I think it's weird that mother is doing nothing.
ไม่มีอะไร ฉันคิดว่ามันแปลกที่แม่ไม่ทำอะไรเลย
That's right. She has so many subordinates, why didn't she send them to attack the Body?
ถูกตัอง. เธอมีลูกน้องมากมาย ทำไมเธอไม่ส่งพวกเขาไปโจมตีร่างกายล่ะ?
Besides, there are Arch Taratects.
นอกจากนี้ยังมี Arch Taratects
If many Arch Taratects attack
ถ้าอาร์คทาราเทคหลายคนโจมตี
at the same time, there's a high chance for them to defeat the Body.
ในขณะเดียวกัน ก็มีโอกาสสูงที่พวกเขาจะเอาชนะร่างกายได้
But if our Body faces that situation, she will escape using Teleport.
แต่ถ้าร่างกายของเราเผชิญกับสถานการณ์นั้น เธอจะหลบหนีโดยใช้เทเลพอร์ต
Escape?
หนี?
Since there's no chance of winning, of course she will escape.
เนื่องจากไม่มีโอกาสชนะ แน่นอน เธอจะหนีรอด
Does mother know this?
แม่รู้เรื่องนี้ไหม?
What?
อะไร?
Mother is linked to us since we were born.
แม่ผูกพันกับเราตั้งแต่เราเกิด
But she can't be monitoring just one family member, right? She has many spiders.
แต่เธอไม่สามารถเฝ้าติดตามสมาชิกในครอบครัวเพียงคนเดียวได้ใช่ไหม เธอมีแมงมุมหลายตัว
Since our existence isn't ordinary, she might have targeted us.
เนื่องจากการดำรงอยู่ของเราไม่ธรรมดา เธออาจมุ่งเป้าไปที่เรา
If that's the case, the last attack...
หากเป็นกรณีนี้ การโจมตีครั้งสุดท้าย...
In order to make us think we have no chance of winning and not have us escape,
เพื่อให้เราคิดว่าเราไม่มีทางชนะและไม่ให้เราหนี
she sent just enough combat power to attack us.
เธอส่งพลังต่อสู้มาเพียงพอที่จะโจมตีเรา
I think mother is very intelligent.
ฉันคิดว่าแม่ฉลาดมาก
If that's the case, it's weird indeed that
ถ้าอย่างนั้นก็น่าแปลกตรงที่
she's not taking any actions.
เธอไม่ได้ดำเนินการใดๆ
Could she be waiting?
เธอรอได้ไหม
What is she waiting for?
เธอรออะไร
How would I know?
ฉันจะรู้ได้อย่างไร?
What's that noise?
นั่นเสียงอะไร?
What is she planning to do?
เธอกำลังวางแผนที่จะทำอะไร?
We're fooled.
เราหลงกล
Contact our Body, hurry!
ติดต่อร่างกายของเรา เร็วเข้า!
Okay.
ตกลง.
It hurts!
มันเจ็บ!
What happened?
เกิดอะไรขึ้น?
I can't pass. I seem to be hindered by mother.
ฉันไม่สามารถผ่าน ดูเหมือนแม่จะขัดขวาง
She blocked our communication with our Body.
เธอปิดกั้นการสื่อสารของเรากับร่างกายของเรา
Is she keeping silent to wait for the chance to block it?
เธอนิ่งเงียบเพื่อรอโอกาสที่จะปิดกั้นหรือไม่?
Then send out all her subordinates at one go.
แล้วส่งลูกน้องของเธอทั้งหมดออกไปในคราวเดียว
Oh my, mother is being serious.
โห แม่พูดจริงจัง
She plans to kill our Body in a breath.
เธอวางแผนที่จะฆ่าร่างกายของเราในลมหายใจ
What do we do?
พวกเราทำอะไร?
We can't do anything.
เราไม่สามารถทำอะไรได้เลย
The person in charge of information, the hypothesis of mother can't go outside
ผู้รับผิดชอบข้อมูลสมมุติแม่ออกนอกบ้านไม่ได้
has been overthrown.
ถูกโค่นล้ม
What should I eat today?
วันนี้ฉันควรกินอะไร
I wonder if there are wild boars or deer in this world.
ฉันสงสัยว่ามีหมูป่าหรือกวางอยู่ในโลกนี้หรือไม่
If there's any, I can cook wild boar or deer hot pot.
ถ้ามี ฉันสามารถปรุงหมูป่าหรือหม้อไฟกวางได้
After that, I can have some delicious fruits.
หลังจากนั้นก็กินผลไม้อร่อยๆ
So exciting!
น่าตื่นเต้นมาก!
I found fruits so quickly.
ฉันพบผลไม้อย่างรวดเร็ว
I didn't expect the dessert to appear first. But it's fine.
ฉันไม่ได้คาดหวังว่าขนมจะปรากฏก่อน แต่ก็ไม่เป็นไร
This is so delicious and sweet. Awesome!
อันนี้อร่อยและหวานมาก เจ๋ง!
It's great to be out.
มันเยี่ยมมากที่ได้ออกไป
The floor is vibrating.
พื้นสั่นสะเทือน
Oh no! I have to escape here.
ไม่นะ! ฉันต้องหนีที่นี่
Why is mother outside?
ทำไมแม่ออกไปข้างนอก?
Monster! She's a monster!
สัตว์ประหลาด! เธอเป็นสัตว์ประหลาด!
"QUEEN TARATECT. WEAKENING. LEVEL 89" She's five times stronger than Araba!
“ราชินีทาราเท็ค อ่อนแอ ระดับ 89” เธอแข็งแกร่งกว่าอราบาห้าเท่า!
How can I defeat her?
ฉันจะเอาชนะเธอได้อย่างไร
Run!
วิ่ง!
Why didn't my parallel wills inform me immediately?
ทำไมพินัยกรรมคู่ขนานของฉันไม่แจ้งให้ฉันทราบทันที?
Hello?
สวัสดี?
Could the communication be blocked?
สามารถบล็อกการสื่อสารได้หรือไม่?
This is bad!
นี้ไม่ดี!
How did she leave the labyrinth? Why does she know I'm here?
เธอออกจากเขาวงกตได้อย่างไร? ทำไมเธอถึงรู้ว่าฉันอยู่ที่นี่?
Although there are much to think about, I should think about them later.
แม้ว่าจะมีเรื่องให้คิดมากมาย แต่ฉันก็ควรคิดถึงพวกเขาในภายหลัง
Use Teleport Magic quickly.
ใช้ Teleport Magic อย่างรวดเร็ว
Although I have Ultimate Wizard skill, teleporting far is still time consuming.
แม้ว่าฉันจะมีทักษะ Ultimate Wizard แต่การเทเลพอร์ตก็ยังใช้เวลานาน
The movement alone is harmful enough, if I was hit I will surely be dead instantly.
แค่การเคลื่อนไหวอย่างเดียวก็อันตรายพอแล้ว ถ้าฉันถูกโจมตี ฉันคงตายทันที
Oh my!
พุทโธ่!
She can attack fiercely while moving. This is cunning.
เธอสามารถโจมตีอย่างดุเดือดขณะเคลื่อนที่ นี่คือไหวพริบ
Hurry up with the magic.
รีบเร่งด้วยเวทมนตร์
I'm going to be caught.
ฉันจะถูกจับ
So close!
เฉียดฉิว!
I can't escape...
ฉันหนีไม่พ้น...
That was close.
มันปิด.
If I were to be one second slower, I would be dead.
ถ้าฉันช้ากว่านี้หนึ่งวินาที ฉันคงตาย
I was wondering why it's so tough to walk.
ฉันสงสัยว่าทำไมมันจึงยากที่จะเดิน
I was finally out. But I can only stay in my old nest before I recover.
ในที่สุดฉันก็ออกมา แต่ฉันทำได้แค่อยู่ในรังเก่าก่อนจะหายดีเท่านั้น
There are two Arch Taratects and many small spiders.
มี Arch Taratects สองตัวและแมงมุมตัวเล็กจำนวนมาก
What?
อะไร?
Them showing up at this point means this is mother's trap.
ที่โผล่มาตรงจุดนี้หมายความว่านี่คือกับดักของแม่
She expected me to teleport home?
เธอคาดว่าฉันจะเทเลพอร์ตกลับบ้าน?
I have perhaps underestimated mother's intelligence.
ฉันอาจประเมินความฉลาดของแม่ต่ำไป
Venom...
พิษ...
Even with my strong endurance, this situation is bad.
แม้จะมีความอดทนอย่างแข็งแกร่ง แต่สถานการณ์นี้ก็แย่
Five of them?
ห้าคน?
Mother, do you really want to kill your child?
แม่ คุณอยากจะฆ่าลูกของคุณจริงๆ เหรอ?
If I didn't have the endurance skill, I would have been dead by now.
ถ้าฉันไม่มีทักษะความอดทน ฉันคงตายไปแล้ว
Once MP value is used up, I will surely be dead.
เมื่อใช้ค่า MP หมด ฉันจะตายอย่างแน่นอน
Fortunately I have Ultimate Wizard skill, my MP value can recover automatically.
โชคดีที่ฉันมีทักษะ Ultimate Wizard ค่า MP ของฉันสามารถกู้คืนได้โดยอัตโนมัติ
Although I won't die so quickly,
แม้ว่าฉันจะไม่ตายเร็วนัก
I might die if I'm injured so badly that I can't recover in time.
ฉันอาจตายได้หากฉันบาดเจ็บสาหัสจนไม่สามารถฟื้นตัวได้ทันเวลา
This situation is becoming worse.
สถานการณ์นี้กำลังแย่ลง
Only in Middle Stratum I can defeat all of them at the same time.
เฉพาะใน Middle Stratum เท่านั้นที่ฉันสามารถเอาชนะพวกมันได้ทั้งหมดในเวลาเดียวกัน
But I have no chance to escape.
แต่ฉันไม่มีโอกาสหนี
Since there's no chance, I have to create it myself.
เนื่องจากไม่มีโอกาส ฉันต้องสร้างมันขึ้นมาเอง
Venomous fog.
หมอกพิษ.
Good. That was successful.
ดี. ที่ประสบความสำเร็จ
It's seen through so soon.
เห็นผ่านไปเร็วจัง
Is there no chance to teleport?
ไม่มีโอกาสในการเทเลพอร์ตหรือไม่?
Very well. I finally got rid of them.
ดีมาก. ในที่สุดฉันก็กำจัดพวกเขา
Next...
ต่อไป...
Let's see who can stand the heat better in Middle Stratum.
มาดูกันว่าใครทนร้อนได้ดีกว่าใน Middle Stratum
I see it.
ฉันเห็นมัน.
What is this? A puppet?
นี่คืออะไร? หุ่นเชิด?
That was fast.
นั่นเร็วมาก.
It can actually use weapons.
สามารถใช้อาวุธได้จริง
This is too powerful.
นี่มันทรงพลังเกินไป
That's the Body.
นั่นคือร่างกาย
Isn't that a very strong little spider?
นั่นไม่ใช่แมงมุมตัวเล็กที่แข็งแรงมากเหรอ?
That is definitely mother's trump card.
นั่นเป็นไพ่ยิปซีของแม่อย่างแน่นอน
The Puppet Taratect is ahead and the Arch Taratects are at the back.
Puppet Taracect อยู่ข้างหน้าและ Arch Taracects อยู่ด้านหลัง
There are even five of them.
มีแม้กระทั่งห้าคน
I lost my front and back legs so I can't move freely.
ฉันสูญเสียขาหน้าและหลังของฉัน ดังนั้นฉันจึงไม่สามารถเคลื่อนไหวได้อย่างอิสระ
They're not giving me the chance to teleport at all.
พวกมันไม่ให้โอกาสผมเทเลพอร์ตเลย
The only way to Middle Stratum is blocked by Puppet Taratect as well.
วิธีเดียวที่จะไปยัง Middle Stratum ถูกบล็อกโดย Puppet Taracect เช่นกัน
This situation is deadlier than the fight with Araba.
สถานการณ์นี้อันตรายกว่าการต่อสู้กับอราบา
I don't want to die!
ไม่อยากตาย!
I will not give up!
ฉันจะไม่ยอมแพ้!
Diablo Bullets!
ดิอาโบล บุลเล็ต!
I will have one eye to see the future.
ฉันจะมีตาข้างเดียวเพื่อดูอนาคต
The rest shall be used for Evil Eyes. Absorb MP level.
ส่วนที่เหลือจะใช้สำหรับ Evil Eyes ดูดซับระดับ MP
Keep firing Diablo Bullets.
ยิง Diablo Bullets ต่อไป
Good. I can keep distance like this.
ดี. รักษาระยะห่างแบบนี้ก็ได้
I must keep this state until I heal. Let's think about the next step.
ฉันต้องรักษาสภาพนี้ไว้จนกว่าฉันจะหายดี ลองคิดถึงขั้นตอนต่อไป
Can I stop them just by using Diablo Bullets?
ฉันสามารถหยุดพวกเขาเพียงแค่ใช้ Diablo Bullets ได้หรือไม่
Diablo Gun!
เดียโบลกัน!
Diablo Bullets!
ดิอาโบล บุลเล็ต!
Cursed you. I can't use Diablo Gun and Diablo Bullets at the same time.
สาปแช่งคุณ ฉันไม่สามารถใช้ Diablo Gun และ Diablo Bullets พร้อมกันได้
If my parallel wills are here, we can shoot together.
ถ้าพินัยกรรมคู่ขนานของฉันอยู่ที่นี่ เรามายิงกัน
It's good that Arch Taratects aren't attacking at the same time,
ดีที่ Arch Taracects ไม่โจมตีพร้อมกัน
but the path to Middle Stratum shouldn't be blocked.
แต่ไม่ควรปิดกั้นเส้นทางสู่ชั้นกลาง
Hey!
เฮ้!
Escaping this way will only make Middle Stratum further away. The leeway is also blocked.
การหลบหนีด้วยวิธีนี้จะทำให้ชั้นกลางห่างออกไปเท่านั้น ทางที่คั่งค้างยังถูกปิดกั้น
It's annoying. Quiet down!
มันน่ารำคาญ. เงียบลง!
I can't find a point to break through. What should I do?
ฉันไม่สามารถหาจุดที่จะเจาะทะลุ ฉันควรทำอย่างไรดี?
It will be great if my level upgrades.
มันจะดีมากถ้าอัพเกรดระดับของฉัน
But I just upgraded. My experience level isn't enough yet.
แต่ฉันเพิ่งอัพเกรด ระดับประสบการณ์ของฉันยังไม่เพียงพอ
Oh, right. Although they're just lackeys,
โอ้ใช่. แม้ว่าพวกเขาจะเป็นแค่ลูกครึ่ง
I defeated many Small Taratects.
ฉันเอาชนะทาราเทคขนาดเล็กจำนวนมาก
This is the power of accumulation.
นี่คือพลังแห่งการสะสม
I think they're the easiest to defeat.
ฉันคิดว่ามันง่ายที่สุดที่จะเอาชนะ
Oh no!
ไม่นะ!
Phoenix Fantasy... No.
ฟีนิกซ์แฟนตาซี...ไม่
"GAIDO MAGIC. FANTASY" Gaido Magic. Fantasy.
"GAIDO MAGIC แฟนตาซี" ไกโดเมจิก แฟนตาซี.
Everything you see is just a delusion.
ทุกสิ่งที่คุณเห็นเป็นเพียงภาพลวงตา
INSIDIOUS
ร้ายกาจ
I left marks on you so I can see clearly.
ฉันทิ้งรอยไว้บนตัวคุณเพื่อให้มองเห็นได้ชัดเจน
Being initiative has a higher chance of winning.
การเป็นผู้ริเริ่มมีโอกาสชนะสูงกว่า
I'm going to win...
ฉันจะชนะ...
This is the puppet's trap.
นี่คือกับดักของหุ่นเชิด
I must break free quickly.
ฉันต้องหลุดพ้นโดยเร็ว
My body is going to be squashed.
ร่างกายของฉันกำลังจะถูกบีบ
I can only use Destructive Evil Eye.
ฉันใช้ได้แต่ตาปีศาจแห่งการทำลายล้างเท่านั้น
But if I still can't defeat the Arch Taratects...
แต่ถ้าฉันยังไม่สามารถเอาชนะ Arch Taratects ได้...
I have no time... to hesitate.
ฉันไม่มีเวลา...จะลังเล
Awesome! Did it work?
เจ๋ง! มันทำงาน?
Seriously?
อย่างจริงจัง?
It can still move after losing half a face?
มันยังเคลื่อนที่ได้หลังจากเสียหน้าไปครึ่งหน้า?
If even this doesn't work, I can only get to the other world.
หากสิ่งนี้ไม่ได้ผล ฉันก็ไปได้เพียงอีกโลกหนึ่งเท่านั้น
I've recovered.
ฉันหายดีแล้ว
Take my venomous fangs!
เอาเขี้ยวพิษของฉันไป!
Okay. Now...
ตกลง. ตอนนี้...
You did notice that I want to attack you.
คุณสังเกตเห็นว่าฉันต้องการโจมตีคุณ
You're planning to kill me with the Arch Taratects, right?
คุณกำลังวางแผนที่จะฆ่าฉันด้วย Arch Taracects ใช่ไหม?
But you're too late.
แต่คุณสายเกินไป
That was close but it was successful.
ใกล้เคียงแต่ก็สำเร็จ
If I don't retreat quickly, I will be burnt to ashes.
ถ้าข้าไม่รีบหนี ข้าจะถูกเผาเป็นเถ้าถ่าน
That was a crucial moment.
นั่นเป็นช่วงเวลาที่สำคัญ
If I made a wrong judgement, I might be dead.
ถ้าฉันตัดสินใจผิด ฉันอาจจะตาย
By the way, the Puppet Taratect wasn't one of the evolution options.
อย่างไรก็ตาม Puppet Taracect ไม่ใช่หนึ่งในตัวเลือกวิวัฒนาการ
Is it a special individual different from the general evolution?
เป็นบุคคลพิเศษที่แตกต่างจากวิวัฒนาการทั่วไปหรือไม่?
Since I can't figure this out, I should start from collecting information about mother.
เนื่องจากผมคิดไม่ออก ผมจึงควรเริ่มจากการรวบรวมข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับแม่
But I still can't contact my parallel wills.
แต่ฉันยังติดต่อพินัยกรรมคู่ขนานไม่ได้
Whatever. I shall evolve first.
อะไรก็ได้ ฉันจะพัฒนาก่อน
Since I still have to fight some unreasonably strong opponents.
เนื่องจากฉันยังต้องต่อสู้กับคู่ต่อสู้ที่แข็งแกร่งอย่างไร้เหตุผล
"EVOLUTION OPTION: ZANA HOROWA" The monsters around here will not come near me.
"EVOLUTION OPTION: ZANA HOROWA" สัตว์ประหลาดแถวนี้จะไม่เข้ามาใกล้ฉัน
I will have Arch Taratects as nutrient source after the evolution. So no problem.
ฉันจะมีอาร์คทาราเทคเป็นแหล่งอาหารหลังวิวัฒนาการ เลยไม่มีปัญหา
Okay. Let's evolve.
ตกลง. มาวิวัฒนาการกันเถอะ
Ede Saines evolves into Zana Horowa.
Ede Saines วิวัฒนาการเป็น Zana Horowa
♫This is annoying. I'm sure I won♫
♫นี่มันน่ารำคาญ ฉันแน่ใจว่าฉันชนะ♫
♫Weak one (swallow it) Strong ones (Exhausted). Take it as nutrition♫
♫ตัวอ่อน (กลืนเข้าไป) ตัวที่แข็งแรง (หมดแรง) ใช้เป็นสารอาหาร ♫
♫"Again! Again!" What a boring game♫
♫"อีกครั้ง!อีกครั้ง!" ช่างเป็นเกมที่น่าเบื่อ♫
♫Don't look down at life♫
♫อย่าดูถูกชีวิต♫
♫Fooled. I knew your intelligence is wrong♫
♫โง่เขลา ฉันรู้ว่าสติปัญญาของคุณผิด♫
♫Tell me how it feels to be fooled by an inferior animal♫
♫บอกฉันทีว่ารู้สึกอย่างไรที่ถูกสัตว์ที่ด้อยกว่าหลอกมา♫
♫I'm still happy over your misery today. I shall start eating now♫
♫ฉันยังคงมีความสุขกับความทุกข์ยากของคุณในวันนี้ ฉันจะเริ่มกินแล้ว ♫
♫Unreasonable, unlucky, so what?♫
♫ไร้เหตุผล โชคร้าย แล้วไงล่ะ♫
♫I want to try my best to live♫
♫I want to try my best to live♫
♫Succeeded. I almost got all of you♫
♫Succeeded. I almost got all of you♫
♫Silk control. Venomous fangs. Sure-win strategy. Watch it♫
♫Silk control. Venomous fangs. Sure-win strategy. Watch it♫
♫Victory! No one can stop me♫
♫Victory! No one can stop me♫
♫Despite the failed reincarnation, I want to keep living♫
♫Despite the failed reincarnation, I want to keep living♫
♫Defeat! Great! Spider! Good!♫
♫Defeat! Great! Spider! Good!♫
♫Defeat! No problem! Spider's style! (Die, die die)♫
♫Defeat! No problem! Spider's style! (Die, die die)♫
Sue...
Sue...
Shun, perhaps this will make you feel better.
Shun, perhaps this will make you feel better.
As long as she's still brainwashed, she won't be killed.
As long as she's still brainwashed, she won't be killed.
If I were more useful, Sue and Katia wouldn't have gone through this.
If I were more useful, Sue and Katia wouldn't have gone through this.
Don't blame yourself.
Don't blame yourself.
If you hadn't saved me with your skill, I would be dead.
If you hadn't saved me with your skill, I would be dead.
Please get over here.
Please get over here.
The situation isn't too optimistic.
The situation isn't too optimistic.
With the control of the church, Prince Hugo is controlling the world.
With the control of the church, Prince Hugo is controlling the world.
If he's left alone like this, the Demon Clan will take advantage of it.
If he's left alone like this, the Demon Clan will take advantage of it.
Hugo seems to be leading a troop to attack the Elf Village.
Hugo seems to be leading a troop to attack the Elf Village.
Then let's get there first to ambush him.
แล้วไปซุ่มโจมตีเขาก่อน
There's a problem.
มีปัญหา
Look.
ดู.
We have to take this path to get to Elf Village from here.
เราต้องใช้เส้นทางนี้เพื่อไปยังหมู่บ้านเอลฟ์จากที่นี่
What's the problem you mentioned?
ปัญหาที่คุณกล่าวถึงคืออะไร?
We have to go through the world biggest labyrinth,The Great Elroe Labyrinth.
เราต้องผ่านเขาวงกตที่ใหญ่ที่สุดในโลก The Great Elroe Labyrinth
That place is inhabited by many dangerous monsters.
สถานที่นั้นเป็นที่อยู่อาศัยของสัตว์ประหลาดอันตรายมากมาย
What about other routes?
แล้วเส้นทางอื่นล่ะ?
There's none.
ไม่มีเลย
It seems we have no other way.
ดูเหมือนว่าเราไม่มีทางอื่นแล้ว
We can't let the country go down without doing anything.
เราไม่สามารถปล่อยให้ประเทศล่มจมโดยไม่ได้ทำอะไรเลย
I would like to go back once again.
ฉันอยากจะกลับไปอีกครั้ง
Shun...
ชุน...
As the true Warrior, you have to fight the fake Warrior who betrayed the humankind.
ในฐานะนักรบที่แท้จริง คุณต้องต่อสู้กับนักรบจอมปลอมที่ทรยศต่อมนุษยชาติ
Fight Prince Hugo.
ต่อสู้กับเจ้าชายฮิวโก้
Of course.
แน่นอน.
SO I'M A SPIDER, SO WHAT? NEXT EPISODE: FLYING, OBTAINED
ฉันเป็นแมงมุม แล้วไง ตอนต่อไป: บิน ได้รับ
STAY TUNED
คอยติดตาม